[{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445576,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":20648,"timeElapsed":134857},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980457126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":11548,"timeElapsed":146407},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482731,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":25602,"timeElapsed":172012},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980495407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":12672,"timeElapsed":184688},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980512296,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":16884,"timeElapsed":201577},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980517468,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":5168,"timeElapsed":206749},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523451,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5977,"timeElapsed":212731},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980531116,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":7657,"timeElapsed":220397},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980541896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"206","question":"Do you lose things easily? What was the most recent thing you lost or misplaced? If you ended up finding it, where did you find it? If not, have you replaced it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":10775,"timeElapsed":231176},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10452,"timeElapsed":244685},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980560680,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5272,"timeElapsed":249961},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980563583,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2901,"timeElapsed":252864},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566416,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2830,"timeElapsed":255697},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569355,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2935,"timeElapsed":258636},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572004,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2648,"timeElapsed":261285},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3021,"timeElapsed":264307},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980577473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2445,"timeElapsed":266754},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2515,"timeElapsed":269274},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":6645,"timeElapsed":309483},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641329,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":21125,"timeElapsed":330610},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980644645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3315,"timeElapsed":333926},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980648090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3441,"timeElapsed":337371},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980651185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3092,"timeElapsed":340466},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980653880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2693,"timeElapsed":343161},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980659003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":5119,"timeElapsed":348284},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980679044,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":20039,"timeElapsed":368325},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980755581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":76535,"timeElapsed":444862},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980758263,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"50","question":"What does it mean to “know” somebody or feel close to them?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":447544},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763251,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3318,"timeElapsed":452532},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794531,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":31278,"timeElapsed":483811},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797476,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2943,"timeElapsed":486757},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980826739,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":29258,"timeElapsed":516020},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980835885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":9141,"timeElapsed":525166},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":7494,"timeElapsed":532664},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848414,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5027,"timeElapsed":537695},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980852947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":4530,"timeElapsed":542228},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2918,"timeElapsed":545147},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980860690,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2887,"timeElapsed":549971},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980865524,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":4830,"timeElapsed":554805},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980868138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2612,"timeElapsed":557419},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870844,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2704,"timeElapsed":560125},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980875274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4429,"timeElapsed":564555},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980877769,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2492,"timeElapsed":567050},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980880119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2348,"timeElapsed":569400},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980883699,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3578,"timeElapsed":572980},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980888321,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4620,"timeElapsed":577602},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980896976,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":6321,"timeElapsed":586257},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980899840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2862,"timeElapsed":589121},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3524,"timeElapsed":592648},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980906885,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":3514,"timeElapsed":596166},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980909949,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3061,"timeElapsed":599230},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980914082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4131,"timeElapsed":603363},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980917852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3765,"timeElapsed":607133},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980921051,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3196,"timeElapsed":610331},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980928115,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7061,"timeElapsed":617396},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980932383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"184","question":"What is your favorite day of the week? Least favorite? Why did you choose these?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":4266,"timeElapsed":621663},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980937775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3897,"timeElapsed":627056},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980940208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2428,"timeElapsed":629489},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980942444,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":2234,"timeElapsed":631725},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980948162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":5717,"timeElapsed":637443},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980950940,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":640221},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980955462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4517,"timeElapsed":644742},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980958908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3443,"timeElapsed":648189},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980962350,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3440,"timeElapsed":651631},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980965119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"210","question":"What was the first thing you ever learned to cook by yourself? Who taught you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":654400},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980970275,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3769,"timeElapsed":659555},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980973146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2869,"timeElapsed":662427},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980975779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2630,"timeElapsed":665060},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980978643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":667924},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980981236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2590,"timeElapsed":670517},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980983561,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2323,"timeElapsed":672842},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980986036,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2472,"timeElapsed":675317},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980988889,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2850,"timeElapsed":678169},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980991565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"121","question":"What is the strangest belief you have ever sincerely held beyond the age of 13?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2672,"timeElapsed":680846},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980997424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3920,"timeElapsed":686705},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981000384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":2956,"timeElapsed":689665},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981003861,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3474,"timeElapsed":693142},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981010188,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":6324,"timeElapsed":699469},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981013165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2976,"timeElapsed":702446},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981017608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":4441,"timeElapsed":706889},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981021052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3440,"timeElapsed":710333},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981025032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3978,"timeElapsed":714312},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028212,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3178,"timeElapsed":717493},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981033099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3381,"timeElapsed":722380},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981036589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3487,"timeElapsed":725870},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981039651,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3060,"timeElapsed":728932},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981044732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5080,"timeElapsed":734013},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981048737,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":4003,"timeElapsed":738018},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981052183,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":741464},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981057660,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":5473,"timeElapsed":746941},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981061363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3702,"timeElapsed":750644},{"subjectID":"4zt1u4zbep","prolificID":"67683198d75a96b91625f22d","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2df45abe568adbb741b","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"83","question":"Is there something about you that you struggle to admit to yourself or confront? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3224,"timeElapsed":753871}]